Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1133b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 3/4 x 9 1/2 inches; Stamped on verso: Peter A. Juley and Son / Photographers of Fine Arts / Since 1896 / 225 West 57th Street - New York City. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. View of 5 paintings on wall. Cropped version of image 2006-06-1133.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1133c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 1/2 x 9 1/4 inches; Stamped on verso: Peter A. Juley and Son / Photographers of Fine Arts / Since 1896 / 225 West 57th Street - New York City. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. Photographed is accompanied by a sheet of paper to which it was once mounted.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1134a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK - 1930.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1134b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK - 1930.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1134c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: Show 32 Dec. 31 - Feb. 32. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK - 1930.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1134d; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 3/4 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK - 1930. Photograph has been mounted but is not correctly aligned.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1134e; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK - 1930.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1135a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 3 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Feb Mar - 30'Handwritten on verso: "Show Feb. Mar. - 30" "I6a" "6" circled
  Interior gallery view of three paintings on a white wall and a painting visible in adjoining room. Paintings on the wall include New York, Night, an abstract landscape, Black Cross, and Ranchos Church No.1.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1137a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 11/16 x 9 5/16 inches; cropped photograph
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1137b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show Feb - Mar. 30. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. View of 4 paintings on wall.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1138a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 5/8 x 8 3/8 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I 8b", "6" (circled)
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York,and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1138b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten on verso: Feb + Mar 1930. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK. Cropped version of 2006-06-1138.
  View of singular painting on the gallery wall, subject is an abstraction of clouds.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1139a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 2 5/8 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I9b"
  Singular image of the painting, Black Cross.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1139b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. View of 3 paintings on wall.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1139c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 2 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. Cropped photograph of 1 painting on wall with a check mark above.
  Image of singular painting of a religious figure as seen through the doorway of an adjoining gallery room.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 27 New Paintings, New Mexico, New York, and Lake George, Interior Gallery View, 1930; 2006.6.1140a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show Feb - Mar - 30. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: OK 1930. Accompanied by a note by O'Keeffe: Should have Bear Lake.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1141a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7/8 x 10 inches; view of 3 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on verso: "I 13 a", "10" (circled), "Show - Jan Feb - 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1142a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I12e","9" (circled); "I 12 a"; "I 12 b"
  Three vertical views of three O'Keeffe paintings; two New Mexican landscapes and a Jackl-in-the-pulpit.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1143a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; view of 5 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on verso: "I 14b", "9" (circled), "Show Jan. Feb. - 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1143b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; view of 5 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on verso: "I 14c", "9" (circled), "Show- Jan. Feb - 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1144a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 1/16 inches; view of 4 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 17b", "9" (circled)
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1144b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on verso: "I 17c", "Show Jan. Feb. 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1145a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; view of 6 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 18b","Show -Jan- Feb. 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1145b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; view of 6 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 18c","Show - Feb. 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1145c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; view of 6 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 18d","9" (circled),"Show -Jan. Feb. 31"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1146a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; view of 6 paintings on wall
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1149a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 4 5/8 inches; Handwritten on recto: p. 354. Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show - 31 - Jan + Feb. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK. Cropped image.
  Corner wall view of O'Keeffe painting of a Pueblo style church with and adobe wall and clouds. Written on the surface of the photograph under the painting in pen is " P.354 " along with a diagonal dark line cutting across the bottom corner of the print.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1152a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 x 4 inches; Handwritten on verso: [Illegible] Ranchos Church - ?. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK. Cropped image.
  Installation view of a version of O'Keeffe's painting of Ranchos de Taos Church.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 33 New Paintings (New Mexico) - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, circa 1931; 2006.6.1154a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view 5 paintings (2 cowskulls); check marks over paintingsHandwritten on recto: check marks Handwritten on verso: "I22a" "11"
  Installation view of five O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent white walls; 2 paintings of horse skulls, one painting of a thigh bone, a painting of a landscape and a painting of a flower.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 33 New Paintings (New Mexico) - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, circa 1931; 2006.6.1155a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 6 11/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on recto: "I23 b"
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent white walls; 2 paintings of horse skulls, one painting of a thigh bone, and a painting of a landscape.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 33 New Paintings (New Mexico) - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, circa 1931; 2006.6.1155b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 3 5/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I23 a" "11" circled
  Installation view of a version of O'Keeffe's painting, Ranchos de Taos Church. On the surface of the photograph in the upper viewer left corner is a diagonal black line.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1156a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 6 3/8 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I24a"
  Installation view of two of O'Keeffe's paintings; a large painting of a cross in the landscape and the painting, Jimson Weed.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1157a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show Jan - Feb. 33. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 1933. View of 4 paintings on wall.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1158a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 6 11/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on recto: indistinguishable markings Handwritten on verso: "I26b"
  Installation view of three O'Keeffe paintings; a painting of a calla lily, a abstract landscape and a painting of flowers.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34)- An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1159a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; view of 6 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Mar - 35'Handwritten on recto: three check marks Handwritten on verso: "I 27a" "Show - Jan .Mar. 35"
  Installation view of O'Keeffe paintings.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1160a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 3/4 x 9 3/8 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1161a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso by O'Keeffe: Show - Jan Mar 35. Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1162a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 5 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 31a" "14"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1163a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 1/8 x 9 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1163b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: ???? Duplicates of Exhibitions - OK.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1164a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 3/16 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall and of large window; black border, wrinkledPrinted on recto: "58 KODAK S AFETY EASTMAN" vertical and reversed Handwritten on verso: "16" circled"I36b"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1165a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall and of large windowPrinted on recto: "58 KODAK S AFETY EASTMAN" vertical and reversed Label on verso: blank
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1165b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Negative of 2006-06-1165.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1167a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 4 15/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on recto: checkmarks Handwritten on verso: "I33" "9" circled
  Installation view of two O'Keeffe paintings on a white wall, Hollyhock White With Pedernal, 1937 and Hollyhock Pink With The Pedernal, New Mexico, 1937.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1167b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 2 7/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on verso: "I35" "9" circled
  Installation view of the O'Keeffe painting, Two White Shells One Black Shell, 1937, on a white wall.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1181a; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7/8 x 10 inches; copy of 2006-06-1181Label on verso: "AS Philadelphia 1944, 1945 404"
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446a; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446b; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446c; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Seven identical copies of the photograph. Printed on verso: " A KODAK PAPER"
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446d; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446e; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches
- Skull, Ghost Ranch, circa 1955; 2006.6.1446f; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1483a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd Show 291 - 1916.
  Installation view of five of O'Keeffe's works on paper mounted on a grey fabric wall separated by chair rail molding with a black pleated skirt. Works from viewer left to right: Train At Night In The Desert, 1916, watercolor and graphite; No. 15 Special, 1916-1917, graphite; double hung watercolors - Sunrise And Little Clouds No. 11, 1916 and Morning Sky With Houses, 1916; and Blue, Green And Red, 1916, watercolor.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1483b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd Show 291 - 1916.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1483c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd Show 291 - 1916.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd Show 291 - 1916.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd Show 291 - 1916.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484c; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd 291.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484d; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd 291.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484e; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd 291.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at 291, Interior Gallery View, 1917; 2006.6.1484f; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Originally housed in a folder labeled in O'Keeffe's handwriting: 2nd 291. View of 2 paintings on wall the 3rd painting has been cut out of the top right corner.
  Installation view of two of O'Keeffe's works on paper mounted on a grey fabric wall separated by chair rail molding with a black pleated skirt. Works from viewer left to right: and abstract composition, No. 8 Special, 1916, charcoal;the third charcoal ( Train At Night In The Desert, 1916) was cut out of the photograph on the viewer right.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Board Meetings, circa 1991; 2006.6.248a; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe Catalogue Raisonne Party (35mm color negatives), circa 1992; 2006.6.269a; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 3 1/2 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake George, circa 1930; 2006.6.716a; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints digital print; Framed.
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Lake George, circa 1930; 2006.6.716b; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints digital print 5 x 5 15/16 inches
  This is a digital print of 2006-06-0716.
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Mary Callery with Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe, 1945; 2006.6.957b; Porter, Eliot Furness, 1909-1990; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 x 8 inches; Framed.